<resources>

    <string name="app_name">DataManager</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">DataManager</string>
    <string name="toggle_data">Data Connection</string>
    <string name="toggle_data_desc">Enable or disable data (3G) connection. You can also enable/disable data outside this application, there won\'t be any conflitcts</string>
    <string name="toggle_data_manager">Data Manager</string>
    <string name="toggle_data_manager_desc">Data Manager will automatically turn on/off data connection after a defined period of time when screen is OFF. Connection will be disabled ONLY if it NOT used. Therefore,  downloads/streaming won\'t be stopped and sync events will be received. Data Mananger will work ONLY if data is activated</string>
    <string name="toggle_wifi">Wifi Connection</string>
    <string name="toggle_wifi_desc">Enable or disable wifi connection. You can also enable/disable wifi outside this application, there won\'t be any conflitcts</string>
    <string name="toggle_wifi_manager">Wifi Manager</string>
    <string name="toggle_wifi_manager_desc">Wifi Manager will automatically turn on/off wifi connection after a defined period of time when screen is OFF. Connection will be disabled ONLY if it NOT used. Therefore,  downloads/streaming won\'t be stopped and sync events will be received. Wifi Mananger will work ONLY if wifi is activated</string>
    <string name="toggle_auto_sync">Auto-Sync Manager</string>
    <string name="toggle_auto_sync_desc">Auto-Sync Manager will disable all synchronizing functions when there are no data connections (3G/Wifi) and screen is OFF. Synchronizing functions will be enabled when data connection will be available</string>
    <string name="toggle_auto_wifi_off">Auto-Wifi Off</string>
    <string name="toggle_auto_wifi_off_desc">Auto-Wifi Off will automatically disable wifi after after a defined period if screen is OFF and no known networks are available</string>
    <string name="time_on">Time On (min)</string>
    <string name="time_on_desc">Number of minutes where data connectivity is ON when screen is shutdown</string>
    <string name="time_off">Time Off (min)</string>
    <string name="time_off_desc">Number of minutes where data connectivity is OFF when screen is shutdown</string>
    <string name="interval_check">Usage check interval (s)</string>
    <string name="interval_check_desc">Number of seconds where the application will check is  data connections (Wifi/3G) are used. A greater value will decrease the chance of interrupting downloads/streaming/syncing but will keep connections alived for longer and thus consume more battery</string>
    <string name="button_save">Save preferences</string>
    <string name="toggle_sleep_hours">Sleep Hours</string>
    <string name="toggle_sleep_hours_desc">During sleep hours all data connections will be desactivated when screen is OFF</string>
    <string name="label_sleep_hours">Sleep Hours :</string>
    <string name="button_change_sleep_hours">Edit</string>
    <string name="label_time_on">Time On(min)</string>
    <string name="label_time_off">Time Off(min)</string>
    <string name="label_time_Interval">Interval Check(sec)</string>
    <string name="label_sleep_off">Connectivity off</string>
    <string name="label_sleep_on">Connectivity on</string>
    <string name="button_save_sleep_hours">Save sleep hours</string>
    
    <color name="white">#FFFFFF</color>
    

</resources>